<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RibbonDiffXml xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <CustomActions />
  <Templates>
    <RibbonTemplates Id="Mscrm.Templates"></RibbonTemplates>
  </Templates>
  <CommandDefinitions />
  <RuleDefinitions>
    <TabDisplayRules />
    <DisplayRules />
    <EnableRules />
  </RuleDefinitions>
  <LocLabels>
    <LocLabel Id="Mscrm_Form_salesorder_MainTab_Actions_CancelOrder_ToolTipDescription">
      <Titles>
        <Title description="Cancel this order and select a status reason. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The status reason shows why the order was cancelled." languagecode="1033" />
        <Title description="إلغاء أمر الشراء هذا وتحديد سبب حالة. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;يعرض سبب الحالة سبب إلغاء أمر الشراء." languagecode="1025" />
        <Title description="Отказ от тази поръчка и избор на описание на състоянието. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Описанието на състоянието показва защо е отказана поръчката." languagecode="1026" />
        <Title description="Cancel·leu aquesta comanda i seleccioneu una raó per a l'estat. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;La raó per a l'estat mostra el motiu pel qual s'ha cancel·lat la comanda." languagecode="1027" />
        <Title description="Umožňuje zrušit tuto objednávku a vybrat důvod stavu. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Důvod stavu označuje, proč byla objednávka zrušena." languagecode="1029" />
        <Title description="Annuller denne ordre, og vælg en statusårsag. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Statusårsagen viser, hvorfor ordren er annulleret." languagecode="1030" />
        <Title description="Dient zum Stornieren dieses Auftrags und zum Auswählen eines Statusgrunds. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Der Statusgrund gibt den Grund für die Stornierung des Auftrags an." languagecode="1031" />
        <Title description="Ακυρώστε αυτήν την παραγγελία και επιλέξτε μια αιτιολογία κατάστασης. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Η αιτιολογία κατάστασης δείχνει γιατί ακυρώθηκε η παραγγελία." languagecode="1032" />
        <Title description="Cancela el pedido y selecciona una razón para el estado. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;La razón para el estado muestra el motivo por el cual se canceló el pedido." languagecode="3082" />
        <Title description="Saate selle tellimuse tühistada ja valida oleku põhjuse. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oleku põhjus näitab, miks tellimus tühistati." languagecode="1061" />
        <Title description="Utzi eskaera hau eta hautatu egoeraren arrazoia. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egoeraren arrazoiak eskaera uzteko arrazoia erakusten du." languagecode="1069" />
        <Title description="Peruuta tämä tilaus ja valitse tilan syy. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tilan syystä näkyy, miksi tilaus peruutettiin." languagecode="1035" />
        <Title description="Annuler cette commande et sélectionner une raison du statut. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;La raison du statut indique pourquoi la commande a été annulée." languagecode="1036" />
        <Title description="Cancelar este pedido e seleccionar unha razón de estado. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Isto mostra o motivo por que foi anulado." languagecode="1110" />
        <Title description="בטל הזמנה זו ובחר סיבת מצב. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;סיבת המצב מראה מדוע בוטלה ההזמנה." languagecode="1037" />
        <Title description="इस ऑर्डर को रद्द करें और एक स्थिति कारण चुनें. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;स्थिति कारण दिखाता है की ऑर्डर क्यों रद्द हुआ था." languagecode="1081" />
        <Title description="Otkažite tu narudžbu i odaberite razlog stanja. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Razlog stanja govori zašto je narudžba otkazana." languagecode="1050" />
        <Title description="A megrendelés visszavonása és az állapot okának beállítása. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Az állapot oka mutatja, hogy miért lett a megrendelés visszavonva." languagecode="1038" />
        <Title description="Batalkan pesanan ini, lalu pilih alasan status. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alasan status akan menunjukkan alasan pembatalan pesanan." languagecode="1057" />
        <Title description="Consente di annullare questo ordine e selezionare un motivo stato. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Il motivo stato indica le ragioni per cui è stato annullato l'ordine." languagecode="1040" />
        <Title description="この受注を取り消し、ステータスを選択します。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ステータスは、受注が取り消された理由を示します。" languagecode="1041" />
        <Title description="Бұл тапсырыстан бас тартып, күй себебін таңдаңыз. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Бұл күй себебі тапсырыстан неліктен бас тартылғанын көрсетеді." languagecode="1087" />
        <Title description="이 주문을 취소하고 상태 설명을 선택합니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;상태 설명은 주문이 취소된 원인을 나타냅니다." languagecode="1042" />
        <Title description="Atšaukti šį užsakymą ir pasirinkti būsenos tipą. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Būsenos tipas rodo, kodėl užsakymas buvo atšauktas." languagecode="1063" />
        <Title description="Atcelt šo pasūtījumu un atlasīt statusa iemeslu. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Statusa iemesls norāda, kāpēc pasūtījums ir atcelts." languagecode="1062" />
        <Title description="Batalkan pesanan ini dan pilih sebab status. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sebab status akan menunjukkan alasan pembatalan pesanan." languagecode="1086" />
        <Title description="Annuller denne ordren, og velg en statusårsak. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Statusårsaken viser hvorfor ordren ble annullert." languagecode="1044" />
        <Title description="Deze order annuleren en een reden van status selecteren. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;De reden van status geeft weer waarom de order is geannuleerd." languagecode="1043" />
        <Title description="Anuluj to zamówienie i wybierz przyczynę stanu. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Przyczyna stanu wskazuje, dlaczego anulowano zamówienie." languagecode="1045" />
        <Title description="Cancele esta ordem e selecione uma razão do status. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A razão do status mostra por que a ordem foi cancelada." languagecode="1046" />
        <Title description="Cancelar esta encomenda e selecionar uma razão do estado. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A razão do estado mostra o motivo pelo qual a encomenda foi cancelada." languagecode="2070" />
        <Title description="Anulați această comandă și selectați un motiv de stare. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Motivul de stare arată de ce a fost anulată comanda." languagecode="1048" />
        <Title description="Отмена этого заказа и выбор состояния. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Состояние показывает причину отмена заказа." languagecode="1049" />
        <Title description="Zruší túto objednávku a vyberie dôvod stavu. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dôvod stavu informuje o tom, prečo bola objednávka zrušená." languagecode="1051" />
        <Title description="Prekličite to naročilo in izberite razlog stanja. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;V razlogu stanja je prikazano, zakaj je bilo naročilo preklicano." languagecode="1060" />
        <Title description="Откажите ову поруџбину и изаберите разлог статуса. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Разлог статуса показује зашто је поруџбина отказана." languagecode="10266" />
        <Title description="Otkažite ovu porudžbinu i izaberite razlog statusa. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Razlog statusa pokazuje zašto je porudžbina otkazana." languagecode="9242" />
        <Title description="Annullera den här ordern och välj en statusorsak. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Statusorsaken visar varför ordern annullerades." languagecode="1053" />
        <Title description="ยกเลิกใบสั่งนี้และเลือกคำอธิบายรายการของสถานะ &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;คำอธิบายรายการของสถานะจะแสดงเหตุผลของการยกเลิกใบสั่ง" languagecode="1054" />
        <Title description="Bu siparişi iptal edin ve bir durum açıklaması seçin. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Durum açıklaması, siparişin neden iptal edildiğini gösterir." languagecode="1055" />
        <Title description="Скасування цього замовлення та вибір опису стану. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Опис стану дає змогу визначити, чому було скасовано замовлення." languagecode="1058" />
        <Title description="Hủy đơn hàng này và chọn lý do dẫn đến trạng thái. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lý do dẫn đến trạng thái cho biết lý do hủy đơn hàng." languagecode="1066" />
        <Title description="取消此订单并选择状态描述。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;状态描述显示了订单取消原因。" languagecode="2052" />
        <Title description="取消此訂單並選取狀態原因。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;狀態原因顯示訂單為何被取消。" languagecode="3076" />
        <Title description="取消此訂單並選取狀態原因。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;狀態原因顯示訂單為何被取消。" languagecode="1028" />
      </Titles>
    </LocLabel>
  </LocLabels>
</RibbonDiffXml>