<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RibbonDiffXml xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <CustomActions />
  <Templates>
    <RibbonTemplates Id="Mscrm.Templates"></RibbonTemplates>
  </Templates>
  <CommandDefinitions />
  <RuleDefinitions>
    <TabDisplayRules />
    <DisplayRules />
    <EnableRules />
  </RuleDefinitions>
  <LocLabels>
    <LocLabel Id="Mscrm_Form_campaignresponse_MainTab_Actions_ConvertResponse_ToolTipDescription">
      <Titles>
        <Title description="Convert a campaign response into a lead, opportunity, or customer record. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can also close the response as Closed or Cancelled." languagecode="1033" />
        <Title description="تحويل استجابة لحملة إلى عميل متوقع أو فرصة مبيعات محتملة أو سجل عميل. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;يمكنك أيضًا إغلاق الاستجابة كـ &quot;مغلقة&quot; أو &quot;ملغاة&quot;." languagecode="1025" />
        <Title description="Преобразуване на даден отговор на кампания в потенциален клиент, възможност или клиентски запис. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Отговорите може също така да се затворят като &quot;Затворени&quot; или &quot;Отказани&quot;." languagecode="1026" />
        <Title description="Converteix una resposta de campanya en un registre de client potencial, oportunitat o client. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;També podeu tancar la resposta com a Tancada o Cancel·lada." languagecode="1027" />
        <Title description="Převede odpověď na kampaň na záznam zájemce, příležitosti nebo zákazníka. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Odpověď lze také zavřít jako uzavřenou nebo zrušenou." languagecode="1029" />
        <Title description="Konvertér en kampagnerespons til en kundeemne-, salgsmuligheds- eller kundepost. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Du kan også lukke svaret som Lukket eller Annulleret." languagecode="1030" />
        <Title description="Dient zum Konvertieren einer Kampagnenreaktion in einen Lead, eine Verkaufschance oder einen Kundendatensatz. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sie können die Reaktion auch als &quot;Geschlossen&quot; oder &quot;Abgebrochen&quot; beenden." languagecode="1031" />
        <Title description="Μετατρέψτε μια απόκριση σε εκστρατεία σε υποψήφιο πελάτη, ευκαιρία ή καρτέλα πελάτη. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Μπορείτε επίσης να κλείσετε την απόκριση με την ένδειξη &quot;Έκλεισε&quot; ή &quot;Ακυρώθηκε&quot;." languagecode="1032" />
        <Title description="Convierte la respuesta de campaña en un registro de cliente potencial, oportunidad o cliente. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;También puede cerrar la respuesta como Cerrada o Cancelada." languagecode="3082" />
        <Title description="Saate teisendada kampaania tagasiside müügivihjeks, müügivõimaluseks või kliendikirjeks. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samuti võite tagasiside sulgeda olekus Suletud või Tühistatud." languagecode="1061" />
        <Title description="Bihurtu kanpainaren erantzuna bezerogai, abagune edo bezero-erregistro. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Erantzuna &quot;Itxitako&quot; edo &quot;Utzitako&quot; gisa itxi dezakezu ere." languagecode="1069" />
        <Title description="Muunna kampanjapalaute liidi-, mahdollisuus- tai asiakastietueeksi. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voit myös sulkea palautteen asettamalla sen Suljettu- tai Peruutettu-tilaan." languagecode="1035" />
        <Title description="Convertir une réponse de campagne en prospect, opportunité ou client. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vous pouvez également fermer la réponse comme Fermée ou Annulée." languagecode="1036" />
        <Title description="Converter unha resposta á campaña en cliente potencial, oportunidade ou rexistro de cliente. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tamén pode pechar a resposta como Pechada ou Cancelada." languagecode="1110" />
        <Title description="המר היענות לקמפיין לרשומת הפניה, הזדמנות או לקוח. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;באפשרותך גם לסגור את ההיענות לקמפיין כסגורה או כמבוטלת." languagecode="1037" />
        <Title description="अभियान प्रत्युत्तर को लीड, अवसर, या ग्राहक रिकॉर्ड में रूपांतरित करें. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;आप प्रत्युत्तर को बंद हो गया या रद्द किया गया के रूप में भी बंद कर सकते हैं." languagecode="1081" />
        <Title description="Pretvorite odaziv na kampanju u potencijalnog klijenta, priliku ili zapis o klijentu. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Možete i zatvoriti odaziv kao Zatvoren ili Otkazan." languagecode="1050" />
        <Title description="Kampányválasz érdeklődővé, lehetőséggé vagy ügyfélrekorddá alakítása. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A válasz Lezárva vagy Visszavonva állapottal is lezárható." languagecode="1038" />
        <Title description="Konversikan respons kampanye ke data prospek, peluang, atau pelanggan. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anda juga dapat menutup respons sebagai Ditutup atau Dibatalkan." languagecode="1057" />
        <Title description="Converti una risposta a campagna in un record di lead, opportunità o cliente. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Puoi inoltre chiudere la risposta come chiusa o annullata." languagecode="1040" />
        <Title description="キャンペーンの反応をリード、営業案件、または顧客レコードに変換します。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;反応を [クローズ済み] または [キャンセル済み] としてクローズすることもできます。" languagecode="1041" />
        <Title description="Науқан сұрауын ықтимал тұтынушы, мүмкіндік немесе тұтынушы жазбасына түрлендіріңіз. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Сұрауды жабық немесе бас тартылған ретінде жабуыңызға болады." languagecode="1087" />
        <Title description="캠페인 반응을 잠재 고객, 영업 기회 또는 고객 레코드로 변환합니다. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;또한 반응을 [종료됨] 또는 [취소됨]으로 종료할 수 있습니다." languagecode="1042" />
        <Title description="Konvertuoti atsaką į kampaniją į galimo kliento, galimybės arba kliento įrašą. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Be to, atsaką galima uždaryti kaip Uždarytas arba Atšauktas." languagecode="1063" />
        <Title description="Kampaņas atbildes pārvēršana par interesenta, iespējas vai klienta ierakstu. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atbildi var arī slēgt, norādot to kā slēgtu vai atceltu." languagecode="1062" />
        <Title description="Tukar respons kempen ke rekod bakal pelanggan, peluang, atau pelanggan. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anda juga dapat menutup respons sebagai Ditutup atau Dibatalkan." languagecode="1086" />
        <Title description="Konverter et kampanjesvar til et emne, en salgsmulighet eller en kundeoppføring. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Du kan også lukke svaret som Lukket eller Avbrutt." languagecode="1044" />
        <Title description="Een campagnerespons converteren naar een potentiële klant, verkoopkans of klantrecord. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;U kunt de respons ook sluiten als gesloten of geannuleerd." languagecode="1043" />
        <Title description="Przekonwertuj odpowiedź na kampanię na rekord potencjalnego klienta, szansy sprzedaży lub klienta. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Można również zamknąć odpowiedź (jako zamkniętą lub anulowaną)." languagecode="1045" />
        <Title description="Converter uma resposta de campanha em um cliente potencial, oportunidade ou registro de cliente. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Também é possível fechar a resposta como Fechada ou Cancelada." languagecode="1046" />
        <Title description="Converter uma resposta à campanha num registo de oportunidade potencial, oportunidade ou cliente. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Também é possível fechar a resposta como Fechada ou Cancelada." languagecode="2070" />
        <Title description="Convertiți un răspuns de la campanie într-un client potențial, o oportunitate sau o înregistrare client. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;De asemenea puteți închide răspunsul ca Închis sau Anulat." languagecode="1048" />
        <Title description="Преобразование отклика от кампании в интерес, возможную сделку или запись клиента. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Можно также закрыть отклик, присвоив ему состояние &quot;Закрыт&quot; или &quot;Отменен&quot;." languagecode="1049" />
        <Title description="Konvertuje odozvu na kampaň na záznam o potenciálnom zákazníkovi, príležitosti alebo zákazníkovi. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Odozvu je tiež možné uzavrieť ako uzavretú alebo zrušenú." languagecode="1051" />
        <Title description="Pretvorite odziv na akcijo v zapis možne stranke, priložnosti ali stranke. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lahko pa tudi zaključite odziv kot »Zaključeno« ali »Preklicano«." languagecode="1060" />
        <Title description="Конвертујте одзив на кампању у потенцијалног клијента, могућност за пословање или запис о клијенту. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Одзив можете и да затворите као затворен или отказан." languagecode="10266" />
        <Title description="Konvertujte odziv na kampanju u potencijalnog klijenta, mogućnost za poslovanje ili zapis o klijentu. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Odziv možete i da zatvorite kao zatvoren ili otkazan." languagecode="9242" />
        <Title description="Konvertera ett kampanjsvar till ett lead, en affärsmöjlighet eller en kundpost. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Du kan också stänga svaret och markera det som stängt eller avbrutet." languagecode="1053" />
        <Title description="แปลงผลตอบรับการส่งเสริมการขายลงในเรกคอร์ดลูกค้าเป้าหมาย โอกาสทางการขาย หรือลูกค้า &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;คุณยังสามารถปิดผลตอบรับเป็นปิดแล้วหรือถูกยกเลิก" languagecode="1054" />
        <Title description="Bir kampanya yanıtını müşteri adayına, fırsata veya müşteri kaydına dönüştürün. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yanıtı Kapatıldı veya İptal Edildi olarak da kapatabilirsiniz." languagecode="1055" />
        <Title description="Перетворити результат кампанії на запис про потенційного клієнта, потенційну угоду або клієнта. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Результат можна також закрити як закритий або скасований." languagecode="1058" />
        <Title description="Chuyển đổi phản hồi về chiến dịch thành khách hàng tiềm năng, cơ hội hoặc bản ghi khách hàng. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bạn còn có thể đóng phản hồi thành Đã đóng hoặc Đã hủy." languagecode="1066" />
        <Title description="将市场活动响应转换为潜在顾客、商机或客户记录。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;您还可以关闭“已关闭”或“已取消”的响应。" languagecode="2052" />
        <Title description="將行銷活動回覆轉換為潛在客戶、商機或客戶記錄。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;您也可以關閉該回覆，視為 [已關閉] 或 [已取消]。" languagecode="3076" />
        <Title description="將行銷活動回覆轉換為潛在客戶、商機或客戶記錄。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;您也可以關閉該回覆，視為 [已關閉] 或 [已取消]。" languagecode="1028" />
      </Titles>
    </LocLabel>
  </LocLabels>
</RibbonDiffXml>